None
!
Eat first!
먼저 드세요!
thank you!
감사합니다!
Who is this tee?
이거 티 누구예요?
It's me!
저입니다!
What could there be?
뭐가 있을까요?
Try something fun!
재밌는 거 좀 해봐요!
Is it fun?
재밌는데?
Board game!
보드게임!
I'm a bit concerned about the content that the CEO is messing around with.
저는 약간 대표님이 잡돌이하는 컨텐츠
You bastard!
잡돌이!
It's so fun!
너무 재밌어요!
We were looking for Kim Yun-ju!
우리가 김윤주를 갈바하더라!
Boss, what are you doing? Are you not working?
사장님 뭐 하시는 거예요? 일 안 해요?
Am I playing?
내가 놀아?
It's not easy, but if you tell me to do it, I have no choice.
쉽지 않지만 시키신다면 어쩔 수 없이
So are people curious?
그럼 사람들이 궁금해하나?
Is that fun?
재밌어하나 그게?
We're just having fun with ourselves!
우리끼리만 깔깔해지시네요!
As viewers, what do we really want to know?
보는 사람들 입장에서 굳이 우리의 뭘 알고 싶어할까?
Do you want to sing?
노래하실래요?
No, that's too magnetic, really!
아니야 그런 건 너무 자기적이야 진짜!
I saw it from a third party perspective!
제 3자 입장으로 봤어요!
What I'm curious about at Wausan is actually something about Kim Yun-ju!
와우산에서 궁금한 건 사실은 김윤주의 어떤 뭔가!
Rather, I think it would be more obvious.
오히려 나 그게 더 뻔할 것 같아
It's not always the city you think it is
그게 항상 네가 생각하는 도시지 아니고
If it comes to you...
너한테만 가면 그걸..
Don't fight!
싸우지 마세요!
Really now...
되게 이제..
The boss is here!
사장님이 나와요!
Ah, it’s noisy now!
아 지금 시끄럽다!
for a moment!
잠깐!
Face the door!
문 마주!
Our Gunderkang should be angry!
우리 건더깡은 화내려야 돼!
The boss is here!
사장님이 나와요!
I'm so nervous!
너무 떨리겠어요!
No, the teacher is here!
아니 선생님이 나와요!
ah..
아..
Do it all with the door closed!
문 닫고 다 해요!
But I don't really do commercial work!
근데 내가 진짜 상용은 안 하잖아!
No commercial use!
상용은 안 하지!
When you open the door, you become nice again!
문 열면 다시 착해져!
Go!
가세요!
Hahahaha
하하하하
This is so burdensome!
이게 되게 부담스럽네요!
This is the first time I've ever looked like this without makeup.
화장을 이렇게 안 하고 뭐 이렇게 나와 본 적이 처음이랄 때
Have you ever tried YouTube?
유튜브 해보신 적 있으세요?
Because that's the only way to communicate with people around you.
하라고 주변에서도 소통할 수 있는 창구가 그거밖에 없으니까
They say I shouldn't do it
해야 되지 않겠냐고 하는데
hmm..
음..
I'm so embarrassed!
너무 쑥스러워요!
Something like that
그런 거
This is a little...
이거 약간..
Aren’t you ashamed of each other? to be honest?
서로 부끄럽지 않아요? 솔직히?
It must be really hot!
되게 더운가 보다!
I'm sweating!
땀난다!
oh my god!
어떡해!
Because you are a celebrity
연예인이셔서
I'm not a celebrity!
연예인 아니에요!
What a celebrity!
무슨 연예인이에요!
no!
아니에요!
just..
그냥..
worker
일하는 사람
huh!
응!
Oppa, why did you come so early?
오빠 왜 이렇게 일찍 왔어?
How many people came?
몇 명 왔어?
Are you all there?
다 왔어?
I'm lying, but Asori asked me that I was 10 minutes late and he came?
거짓말하지만 아소리 10분 늦는다고 나한테 묻자 왔거든?
This is such a serious lie!
거짓말이 이렇게 심해요!
It's been over 10 years with my violin oppa.
바이올린 오빠랑도 10년이 넘었거든요
My bass oppa has been there for over 8 years too.
베이스 오빠도 한 8년 넘었고
It's like a real family!
진짜 가족 같아요!
If the oppa who called me is happy, I am very unhappy.
이 전화한 오빠가 행복하면 제가 너무 불행하고요
When my brother is unhappy, I become very happy.
저 오빠가 불행하면 제가 너무 행복해져요
Everyone, our book is out!
여러분 우리 책이 나왔어요!
thank you!
네 감사합니다!
Wow, it’s pretty!
우와 예쁘다!
Shall we start with that person?
그런 사람부터 가볼까요?
Just about Just about
막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막
I feel like you're chasing me today.
오늘 저를 쫓아가시는 것 같아요
It feels like close coverage today.
오늘 밀착 취재 같은 느낌입니다
What is your schedule in the morning?
오전에는 일정이 어떻게 되시나요?
The stage setting is the highest.
무대 세팅이 제일 높은 거예요
The artist is the most important, today
아티스트가 제일 중요하죠, 오늘은
Even if I speak harshly, please package it nicely.
제가 말을 빡세게 해도 예쁘게 포장해주세요
The CEO might not like it.
대표님이 싫어하실 수도 있거든요
They always say that.
맨날 말을 그렇게 하네요
As you prepare for the performance, please say a few words.
공연 준비하시면서 소감 한마디만
I think I believe it
믿을 것 같습니다
What worries you the most every time you prepare like this?
이렇게 준비할 때마다 가장 걱정되는 게 뭐세요?
It's time
시간이요
When rehearsals are slow, I get too busy.
리허설이 축박하면 너무 분주해지죠
heart
마음이
Our daily wage is 100 for all employees.
저희는 모든 직원이 다 일당 100입니다
There are only four employees.
직원 네 분 밖에 없잖아요
appeared
등장
Coffee is my coffee too
커피도 제 커피
So what do you think? Are you preparing for our performance?
그럼 어떠세요? 우리 공연 준비하시는 거?
I feel so good
너무 기분이 좋고요
I think it will be a happy time
행복한 시간이 될 것 같습니다
Actually, I'm out of my mind.
사실 뭐 정신이 없어요
But I wrote the story like this
근데 이렇게 얘기를 썼어요
How are you preparing for the performance?
공연 준비하신 거 좀 어떠세요?
I'm so nervous
너무 떨려요
It's been so long since I stood on stage
무대에 서는 게 너무 오랜만이고
I'm really the only one who's good at it
진짜 저만 잘하는 거
So I was originally good at studying.
그래서 저 공부도 원래 잘했거든요
But I couldn’t take the CSAT
근데 수능을 못 봐서
I'm not making excuses.
제가 변명하는 게 아니에요
And that song is really good
그리고 저 노래 진짜 잘해요
We were going to be interviewed on the day of the concert, but we were very scared.
공연장 날 저희가 인터뷰 타려고 했는데 많이 무서워서
We all had a bit of a meltdown at that time.
그때 저희가 다 약간 멘붕이었어
There was a lot of delay than expected
생각보다 많이 딜레이가 돼서
I'm worried
걱정이 됩니다
wait a minute
잠시만요
Wear it alternately even when sitting
앉아도 번갈이 신고
yes
네
thank you
감사합니다
sad and happy
슬픈과 행복
막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 Just about
막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막
It's hard. It's hard to do everything from A to Z, and I have to take charge of things like directing, and I have to do it again and again, so I think I've gotten over 100 calls.
힘들죠. A부터 Z까지 하는 게 힘들고 연출 같은 거 맡아서 해야 되고 또 해야 되고 이러다 보니까 전화를 오면 진짜 100통 넘게 받은 것 같아요.
After finishing, I go to see the performance. A performance?
끝나고 공연 보러 갑니다. 공연이요?
Rooftop Dalbi. Wauseon Records performance.
옥상달비. 와우선 레코드 공연.
I said wow, can I really do this, but it's already finished. I see.
와 이거 진짜 할 수 있나라고 했는데 벌써 끝났네. 그러네요.
It's amazing that it turned out like this, and it was harder than I thought.
이렇게 됐다는 게 신기하고 생각보다 힘들었다.
It's hard. How was your day today?
힘들군요. 오늘 하루 어떠셨나요?
Life isn't easy. I must succeed. What and so on. Yes.
인생이 쉽지 않구나. 성공해야겠구나. 뭐 등등. 그렇습니다.
I don't think it would be enough to say thank you 100 times, but please support everything we do at Ausan in the future.
고맙다는 말은 100번을 해도 모자랄 것 같기는 한데 앞으로 또 아우산에서 하고 있는 모든 것들 응원해 주시고
Isn't that bad? I feel like I'm starving to death. I'll be there quickly.
나세진 거 아니에요? 배고파서 죽어버릴 것 같아요. 빨리 가겠습니다.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
고생하셨습니다. 고생하셨습니다.
Heenam is fun. Heenam.
희남이 재밌어. 희남.
Am I the only one who lost too much blood?
나만 너무 피가 나간 거 아닌 거야?
Instead, I should have done it like you did.
그게 아니라 너처럼 했어야 돼.
Oh, I'm not thinking like this, I should be more careful now.
아 이제 좀 자중해야겠다 이렇게 생각하는 거 아니야.
No, no, you know I'm taking pictures.
아니 아니 자큐 찍는 거 알잖아.
Actually, I just want this video to be funny.
사실 저는 이 영상이 그냥 웃겼으면 좋겠어요.
Is there any content you would like to capture?
찍어보시고 싶은 콘텐츠 있으세요?
Our running...
저희 러닝..
Running, right?
러닝이죠?
A reporter from Wausan Artists suggested that we run a marathon.
와우산 아티스트들 기자가 마라톤 대회 한번 나가보자고 제안을 주셔가지고
I think there would be a lot of interest if all artists played.
아티스트 전체가 다 뛴다고 하면 관심 좀 많이 가질 것 같은데
Preparatory line.
준비사선.
I hate it so much.
너무 싫죠.
We can ride on our own.
우리는 자절로 타면 돼.
Put it right behind the CEO and hold that megaphone.
대표님 뒤에 딱 태우고 대표님 그 메가폰 들고
Now, if you run quickly.
자 빨리빨리 뛰면.
no. I'll take a picture. Run.
아니요. 제가 찍을게요. 뛰세요.
I don't go right away because I'm not interested at all.
관심이 전혀 안 가시니까 바로 잘 안 가요.
Climbing again.
또 등산.
Let’s go to Wausan again with the guardians of Mt. Wausan.
저희가 또 그리고 와우산 지킴이어가지고 또 와우산 한번 가보자.
Go to Mt. Wausan and pick up some trash.
와우산 가서 쓰레기라도 집고 오던가.
I've been meaning to do this since I first started the company.
회사 처음 만들 때부터 하려고 하긴 했었어요.
Grab your sweaty content now.
땀 흘리는 콘텐츠를 지금 싹둑싹둑.
just..
그냥..
Oh us?
아 우리?
I just know everything so well that I want to show something through video.
그냥 다 너무 잘 알아가지고 영상으로 뭔가 보여줄만 하고
Another thing I don’t want to do.
또 하기 싫은 거.
Something you don’t want to do?
하기 싫은 거?
I can't do it. mountain climbing.
못하겠다. 등산.
What do you want to do?
너 뭐 하고 싶을게?
We ate steamed chicken downstairs.
우린 밑에서 찜닭에다 닭 먹고.
He said he was eating something and he said it was good.
지금 뭐 먹는다고 하는데 좋다고 했는데.
For the first time, I held on to the rope and climbed up.
저 처음 분산하는데 줄 잡고 올라왔어요.
But why am I not losing weight?
근데 왜 살이 안 빠지냐?
Go down and see Baekchungmok.
내려가서 백충목을.
Ah, this is why Baekchungmuk is like this.
아 백충목을 이래서.
If you run, will you collapse?
런닝하시면 쓰러지시겠는데요?
I ran very well again.
또 달리기 또 엄청 잘.
It seems like it runs a bit like an ostrich.
약간 타조처럼 뛰나봐요.
I need to show you.
보여줘야겠네.
now.
지금.
Just once.
한 번만.
Get some movement.
좀 움직이게 되세요.
Tatak.
따똁.
ah.
아.
Just about Just about
막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막
I almost went to heaven with this, but haru
이걸로 하늘나라에 갈 뻔했다가 하룰라라
Luckily he didn't die
다행히 죽지는 않았고
I was surprised that Yunju jumped better than I thought, thinking she couldn't jump.
윤주가 못 뛸 줄 아는 생각보다 너무 잘 뛰어서 놀랐고
Did you know I couldn’t run?
못 뛸 줄 아셨어요?
Have you never run before?
너도 한 번도 안 뛰지 않았어?
That's right
맞죠
I've never run, that's right
한 번도 안 뛰었다 그래가지고
Would you let the person in first place leave work first?
1등 한 사람 퇴근 먼저 시켜주시냐고
Without any corruption of words
말 변질 없이
I'm still working after work.
퇴근이 아직 일하는 중인데
So this isn't work, but it's strange.
그러니까 이건 일 아닌데 이상하네
Are you eating something delicious? Just one bite?
맛있는 거 드시네요? 한 입만?
and
와
There are fewer people than you think who don't do it.
생각보다 안 하고 오시는 분들이 없네요
No one recognizes me
저 아무도 못 알아봐요
Run at your own pace today
오늘 너의 페이스대로 달려줘
Then just go away, just go far away
그럼 그냥 가버려 그냥 멀리
Then it has no meaning.
그러면 의미가 없잖아요
If I run fast at my own pace and come back quickly
제 페이스대로 빠르게 뛰고 빠르게 오면
Get off work quickly?
빠르게 퇴근?
yes
그렇지
Is the opinion to run something that the director expressed?
러닝하자는 의견은 이사님 내신 의견이에요?
Oh yes
어 그렇습니다
What do you think about running after work?
퇴근 후에 러닝하는 거 어떻게 생각하세요?
I love it so much
너무 좋아요
really
진짜로
And also enjoying this together
또 이 또한 같이 즐기는 게
I think it helps my work life in many ways.
여러모로 회사 생활에 도움이 되는 거 같아요
work overtime until 9 o'clock
9시까지 야근하기
I get off work at 6 and go for a 2 hour run.
6시에 퇴근해서 2시간 러닝하기
If you run, you don’t get paid, right?
러닝하면 수당 안 나오죠?
ah
아
Because it’s a hobby
취미니까
Oh that's right
아 그렇죠
Then you said you would drink it.
그럼 우러마신다고 했잖아요
Then I stay until 9 o'clock
저는 그럼 9시까지
two
둘
three
셋
Have you already come to look up to me?
벌써 우러마왔네?
Do you want me to know this?
이거 알았으면 돼?
hi
안녕
I really like Charlie's chocolate bankbook right now
나 지금 너무 찰리의 초콜릿 통장
Hahahaha
하하하하
Now, if you run
일단 이제 뛰다 보면
I think it's good because I don't have any random thoughts.
잡생각이 없어서 좋은 거 같아요
What happened if you picked it back there?
저기 뒤에 고르면 어떻게 됐어요?
I'm going to run slowly, so go fast
천천히 뛸 거라고 빨리 가라고
Oh, you're dead.
아 작살났군요
Wowsa is a real game play.
와우사는 진짜 게임 플레이이네요
But I guess you have no choice but to do that when you run.
근데 러닝하면 그렇게 할 수밖에 없는 거 같아요
start
시작
There's only one promise
단 한 가지 약속은
There is definitely an end
틀림없이 끝이 있다는 거
Oh no
어 없어요
After it's over
끝난 뒤에
Enough to enjoy it
즐겨울 만큼
Are you running?
뛰어요?
You have to run
뛰셔야죠
I almost have it
거의 갖고 있습니다
I'm running too much
너무 뛰고 있어
Hahahaha
하하하하
I feel like I'm running too much
너무 뛰는 것 같네요
Since then
그때로 해서
I thought you would leave and come back when no one was there.
사람 없는 대로 갔다 올 줄 알았거든요
But when I started
그런데 시작하니까
This won't work
이거 안 되겠다
Oh, I threw it away.
아 버린 거네요
then
그러면
Because the levels are all so different
레벨이 다 너무 다르니까
Oh, you threw it away
아 버리셨네
I can't run
못 뛰겠다
Hahahaha
하하하하
How to throw it away quickly?
어떻게 빠르게 버릴까요?
Now now?
지금 이제?
Oh yes
아 네
Please help me, the writer.
작가님 좀 구해주세요
Author
작가님
Please find it
찾아주세요
Our writer
우리 작가님을
There are a lot of later generations.
이후대가 많네
Do you think I'm lost now?
나 지금 길을 잃어버린 것 같은데?
Let me try to cover the news.
제가 한번 뉴스 취재 해볼게요
Are you going for the second round?
2차로는 하러 가시는 거예요?
There is a challenge in the second lane.
2차로가 도전이 있네요
sorry
죄송합니다
Then, if you buy me Jjamppong, I will do it.
그럼 짬뽕 사주시면 할게요
If you gain 5 kg at your own pace, you can eat sweet and sour pork with Jjamppong.
5키로 제 페이스로 뜨시면 짬뽕에 탕수육
Jjajangmyeon and Jjajangmyeon
짜장면도 짜장면도
I think I should go back
돌아가야 될 것 같아요
Appeared in the 1st round
1차에서 등장
First of all, am I leaving work?
일단 제가 퇴근하는 거예요?
It's not me
나 아닌데
Shall we cross?
건너까요?
Are you able to leave work?
퇴근하실 수 있는 거죠?
uh? Doesn't the day start now?
어? 이제 하루 시작 아니에요?
I need to ask you a favor.
한번 부탁드려 봐야죠
Hey, you are really the worst.
야 너 진짜 최악이다
First of all, when do you get off work?
우선 언제 퇴근을 하시는 건지?
I don't do it, I don't do it
안 해요 안 해요
After hearing this, I don't want to order it.
이 얘기 들으니까 안 시키고 싶어요
great
좋아요
and
와
Just about Just about
막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막 막
thank you
감사합니다.